On your local machine, navigate to the folder where your repository was cloned.
Create a new text file called learning.txt.
In the file, write a short paragraph about something you’ve learned so far in this course.
Work on tasks that will guide you through essential version control concepts, such as forking repositories, creating branches, collaborating with others through pull requests, and managing repositories, both locally and remotely. These tasks are designed for absolute beginners and are applicable to learners from all disciplines—not just software developers or data scientists.
